易考范文二十二
What we can see in the picture is a young woman,
who stands for the online dealers,
is blowing a balloon with the word
“commitment” on it. While a consumer shrinks
at the sight of this giant balloon,
fearing that it might burst.
Obviously, this picture aims to criticize
those dishonest online businesses
which induce people to buy with empty promises.
Shopping on the Internet has become an ingredient
of our life thanks to the prevalence of the cyberspace.
The superiority of online shopping is evident.
People can compare prices without bothering
to walking from one shop to another
and make decisions independent of salespeople's
endless persuasion. They can just settle themselves
in a comfortable chair, have a cup of tea,
click the mouse, and then everything is arranged.
Nevertheless, sometimes shoppers find the products
they receive are different from
those shown on the computer screen;
what's more, if goods they buy from
the Internet are defective,
it will be hard to demand a refund.
As this issue has drawn attention in a wide range,
every effort is made to improve online shopping.
It is good to know that most shops
in the cyberspace are evaluated
by a customer appraisal system,
because of which honesty has become
a matter of self-interest for them.
In addition, it is suggested that online shoppers
be well-informed and cautious before making buying decisions.